(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T03:12:36.993754",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Notice to Attendees: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
Second Round Merchandise
holoplus 大神ミオジャック！してみた！
Hijacked Ookami Mio on holoplus!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start shortly. Please wait.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です
Vocal cheering is permitted.
Ookami Mio 1st Live. "OUR SPARKLE" 二次販売グッズ
Ookami Mio 1st Live "OUR SPARKLE" Second-Round Merchandise Sales
ミオファライト、マフラータオル、Tシャツ、トートバッグなど
Miofa Light, Towel, T-shirt, Tote Bag, and more
キャンバスアート、アクリルペンライトスタンド、キーホルダー、マグカップ
Canvas Art, Acrylic Penlight Stand, Keychain, and Mug
協賛：みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Sponsor: Miruhako by JOYSOUND
よっしゃー！
Yeah!
あ、こっちこっちこっち！
Ah, over here! Over here!
今日、二人じゃないんですか？
Wait, isn't it just the two of you today?
え？二人？
Huh? Two of us?
さっきの...
The ones from earlier...
ここで会った人たち
...the people we met here.
え？
Huh?
心で...
In my heart...
Joyにいこうぜ！
Let's go to Joy!
JOYSOUND X1
holoplus 大神ミオジャック！してみた！
holoplus Ookami Mio Takeover!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
二次販売グッズ 受付中
Second round of merchandise sales now open!
大神ミオ 1st Live「OUR SPARKLE」
[Ookami Mio 1st Live: OUR SPARKLE]
本日は 大神ミオ 1st Live「Our Sparkle」に ご来場いただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you all for coming to Ookami Mio's 1st Live "Our Sparkle" today!
うちうち！うちだよ！大神ミオだよ！
Uchi-uchi! It's me! It's Ookami Mio!
わー みんな元気だー！
Wow, everyone's so energetic!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために いくつかご案内させていただきます
To ensure you enjoy the concert until the very end, I have a few announcements to make.
はーい！元気いいねー
Yay! You're in high spirits!
公演中の撮影 録音 録画機材の使用は 固くお断りいたします
Photography, audio recording, and video recording are strictly prohibited during the show.
万が一 具合が悪くなってしまった場合は 無理をせず 近くのスタッフへおしらせください
Should you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
はーい！
Okay?
会場内でのモッシュ ダイブ 大きく飛び跳ねる ステージに物を投げ込むなど
Moshing, diving, excessive jumping, throwing items onto the stage,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり 公演を妨げる行為は 一切禁止です
and any acts that cause a nuisance or disrupt the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
はーい！守っていただけない場合は ご退場いただく可能性もあるので気をつけてね
If you fail to follow the rules, you may be asked to leave, so please be careful!
また 本公演は映像配信および 写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り
Additionally, cameras for live streaming and photography are operating in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます
and the audience may be captured on screen.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに 使用される可能性がございますので あらかじめご了承ください
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
はーい！みんな良い子だね
Great! You are all such good kids.
あ、ライブのハッシュタグはミオスパークルです
Ah, the hashtag for the concert is #MioSparkle.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてね！
Use the hashtag to build up the excitement!
それでは、開演までもうすぐです！
Well then, it's almost time for the show!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がってこう！
Let's all get excited together!
もしも出会った頃の思い出や感情が遠くに行っても
Even if the memories and feelings from when we met fade far away,
ah もう君のこと忘れたくないよと切なにそう思うよ
Ah, I don't want to forget you, I think so earnestly...
段々暗い夜の隙間に人熱と歓声
Gradually, in the gaps of the dark night, human warmth and cheers,
導火線伝ってさふくらんだ想い打ち上がれ
travel down the fuse, let the swelling feelings soar.
とりどり花を咲かせて スパークル
Blooming colorful flowers, sparkle!
大事なものを見つけたよ
I found something precious,
巡り会えたんだ 君と重なった
we finally met, overlapping with you.
セツナライト 運命が光る 永遠に瞬く色
Setsuna Light, destiny shines in colors that twinkle eternally.
どんな場所に居たっていい メッセージを宇宙の果てだとしても
No matter where we are, even if the message is at the edge of the universe...
ah でも擦れ違い離れた点と点 そばに居たいだけなのに
Ah, but we are points that missed each other and drifted apart, even though I just want to be by your side.
君のこと全部分かってるなんて言う日は来ないけど
A day when I can say I know everything about you will never come, but...
日毎に指折り知ってゆきたくて見つめるんだ
day by day, I count the days to know you more, so I gaze at you.
何千個の星が空を駆けてく
Thousands of stars run through the sky,
消えないでって手を伸ばしたよ
don't fade away, I reached out my hand.
何億の分岐点超えて来たんだろう
How many hundreds of millions of turning points did we cross to get here?
セツナライト 一瞬が光る 奇跡みたいな色
Setsuna Light, a single moment shines in a color like a miracle.
誰もが息をのんで輝き見惚れている華やぐ気配の中で
In the lively atmosphere where everyone holds their breath, fascinated by the radiance,
僕はただ泣きそうでこの瞬間をずっと覚えていたかったんだ
I felt like I was about to cry, wanting to remember this moment forever.
とりどり花を咲かせて スパークル
Blooming colorful flowers, sparkle!
大事なものを見つけたよ
I found something precious,
巡り会えたんだ 君と重なった
we finally met, overlapping with you.
セツナライト 運命が光る
Setsuna Light, destiny shines,
壊れないようにそっと抱きしめた
I gently held it tight so it wouldn't break...
永遠に瞬く色
twinkling eternally.
もしも出会った頃の思い出や感情が遠くに行っても
Even if the memories and feelings from when we met fade far away,
ah もう君のこと忘れたくないよと切なにそう思うよ
Ah, I don't want to forget you, I think so earnestly...
段々暗い夜の隙間に人熱と歓声
Gradually, in the gaps of the dark night, human warmth and cheers,
導火線伝ってさふくらんだ想い打ち上がれ
travel down the fuse, let the swelling feelings soar.
とりどり花を咲かせて スパークル
Blooming colorful flowers, sparkle!
大事なものを見つけたよ
I found something precious,
巡り会えたんだ 君と重なった
we finally met, overlapping with you.
セツナライト 運命が光る 永遠に瞬く色
Setsuna Light, destiny shines in colors that twinkle eternally.
どんな場所に居たっていい メッセージを宇宙の果てだとしても
No matter where we are, even if the message is at the edge of the universe...
ah でも擦れ違い離れた点と点 そばに居たいだけなのに
Ah, but we are points that missed each other and drifted apart, even though I just want to be by your side.
君のこと全部分かってるなんて言う日は来ないけど
A day when I can say I know everything about you will never come, but...
日毎に指折り知ってゆきたくて見つめるんだ
day by day, I count the days to know you more, so I gaze at you.
何千個の星が空を駆けてく
Thousands of stars run through the sky,
消えないでって手を伸ばしたよ
don't fade away, I reached out my hand.
何億の分岐点超えて来たんだろう
How many hundreds of millions of turning points did we cross to get here?
セツナライト 一瞬が光る 奇跡みたいな色
Setsuna Light, a single moment shines in a color like a miracle.
OUR SPARKLE
Ookami Mio 1st Live
静寂に響いてよ my howling
Ring out in the silence, my howling
大神ミオ1st Live、始まるよ！
Ookami Mio's 1st Live is starting!
はい！はい！
Yeah! Yeah!
淡々と流れていく風景
The scenery flowing by uneventfully...
刹那的な日々の中で
...amidst these fleeting days.
差し伸べられた手は優しく
The hand reached out to me was gentle...
鼓動に滴る微熱の予感
...a premonition of a slight fever dripping with my heartbeat.
風に逆らう そう生きてきたから
Rebelling against the wind, because that's how I lived...
君に会って気づく
...I realized when I met you...
「もう一人じゃない」
...\"I am no longer alone.\"
赤光 瞬きは弧描き 月へ 響く
The crimson light, twinkling, arches and echoes to the moon.
爪弾く道 金瞳の群れ 共に嘆く 夜
Plucking the path, the golden-eyed pack laments together in the night.
悲哭 伝播する 想いは 心強くする
Wailing, propagating feelings make my heart stronger.
ついておいでよ
Come follow me...
うしろに君がいるから
...because you are behind me...
私は迷わない
...I will not hesitate...
光射す道へ
...towards the light-filled path!
無力だから 仲間を求め
Because I am powerless, I seek companions.
凍えるから 火を灯して
Because I am freezing, light the fire.
変化とともに 進化していく
Evolving along with the changes...
この結末は 誰も知らない
...no one knows how this will end.
君を信じる そう決めているから
I believe in you, because I've decided to...
どんな 異常 非常も
...no matter how abnormal or extraordinary...
乗り越えられるよ
...we can overcome it!
月光 この闇に唯一 凛と咲く華
Moonlight, the only flower blooming with dignity in this darkness.
恐れなのか 憧れなのか
Is it fear, or is it longing?
向かい合う夜空
Facing the night sky...
大地を駆け抜ける
...running across the earth...
私と君が創り出す
...you and I will create...
この物語 単純な未来じゃない
...this story, it's not a simple future.
湧き立つ情熱 この声に乗せよう
Let's put this welling passion into this voice.
空翔ぶ 羽根なくても
Even without wings to fly in the sky...
手は繋げられたから
...since our hands are held together...
この運命を選んだ
...I chose this destiny.
連動する遠吠えは静寂に響いて
The synchronized howls ring out in the silence.
何度も 何度も
Over and over again...
その絆を確かめ合った
...we confirmed that bond.
瞬きは超えてゆく
A blink of an eye transcends...
月へ響く
...echoing to the moon.
爪弾く
Plucking the strings...
金堂の群ら 共に嘆く夜
...the golden halls mourn together on this night.
慟哭
Wailing...
伝播する思いは 心強くする
...the spreading feelings make my heart stronger.
共に往こうよ 隣に君がいるから
Let's go together, because you are by my side.
私は迷わない 光射す道へ
I will not hesitate on the path where the light shines.
おおかみが止まることはない
The wolf will never stop.
まだまだ走るよ！
I'm still gonna keep running!
みんなついてきて！
Everyone, follow me!
何処まで往こうか ネイビーな夜空に
How far shall we go? Into the navy night sky...
映る過去の自分
...my past self is reflected.
夢見がちだったベイビーフェイスに
To the baby face that used to dream...
サヨナラ？
...should I say goodbye?
見たくないモノ照らすハイビームに
Facing the high beam that illuminates what I don't want to see,
走る焦燥感
a rush of impatience runs through me.
跳ね除けて前へ往けば
If I brush it aside and move forward,
信号は皆色を
the traffic lights will all lose their colors...
無くし消えた
...and disappear.
確かめたい この道が繋ぐ場所を
I want to make sure of the place this path connects to.
深く、深く紺になる
Becoming deeper and deeper navy,
夜を往ける この加速度
I can go through the night at this acceleration...
光さえ超えてゆける 程に
...enough to even surpass the light.
強く、強く踏み込んで
Stepping on it harder and harder,
僕は駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I run, heading straight forward...
譲れない想いを抱いて
...holding onto these unyielding feelings.
標識だらけの街を
Slipping out of the town...
抜け出して
...filled with signs...
未来を探してた
...I was searching for the future.
常識も何も全部
Common sense and everything else...
雑踏と化してた
...had turned into a bustle.
「何処まで往けるの」なんて
"How far can you go?"
聞き飽いた台詞 吐いて
Spitting out that phrase I'm tired of hearing,
曇った窓ガラスに書いた
on the foggy windowpane, I wrote...
本音 すぐに指で消した
...my true feelings, then immediately erased them with my finger.
臆病でも
Even if I'm a coward,
揺るぎない軌跡
an unwavering trajectory...
確かな願いを 胸に 遥か遠く
...and a certain wish are in my heart, far, far away.
錆び付くように軋んでも
Even if it creaks as if rusting,
この真っ暗を灯し進む
I will light up this pitch darkness and move forward.
ただ一つ 答を追いかけて
Chasing after only one answer.
脆くても良い この腕で
Even if it's fragile, with these arms...
掴む為に 手を伸ばすよ
...I'll reach out my hands to grasp it.
打ち鳴らす鼓動の限り
As long as my heart beats.
何度
How many times...
この道で迷って
...have I gotten lost on this path...
見失って どこへ往くの
...and lost sight of where I'm going?
目指す場所も その意味も
Though both the place I aim for and its meaning...
一つしか無いのに
...are only one.
曇った視界は
The foggy vision...
夜に溶けて もう一度
...melts into the night, and once again...
ひらけてゆく
...it opens up.
視線の先
Beyond my gaze,
僕を連れて往くよ きっと
it will surely take me along.
みんな、いくよ！
Everyone, let's go!
深く、深く紺になる
Becoming deeper and deeper navy,
息を吸って今 加速を
taking a breath, I accelerate now...
傷付く程に 強く強くなって
...becoming stronger and stronger to the point of getting hurt.
確かな色 動き出す
A certain color begins to move.
纏ってゆけ その身体で
Wrap it around your body...
鮮やかな夜空の果てへ
...to the end of the vivid night sky...
忘れないように
...so you won't forget.
深く、深く紺になれ
Become deeper and deeper navy.
今を生きる この加速度
Living in the present, at this acceleration...
光だって 超えてゆける 場所へ
...to a place where we can even transcend light.
強く、強く踏み込んで
Stepping on it harder and harder,
僕を駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I run, heading straight forward...
譲れない想いを抱いて
...holding onto these unyielding feelings.
Holding onto my unyielding feelings,
止まらないで
without stopping,
走り続ける意味を知るから
because I know the meaning of running forward...
きっと未来は色に溢れ
The future will surely overflow with color,
まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める
dyeing this yet-unseen world in color.
もっと自由になりたいから
Because I want to be even more free,
ずっと ずっと ずっと夢見てるの
I'll keep on dreaming forever and ever.
空に光る星のように
Like the stars shining in the sky,
輝きたいと願う夜
this is the night I wish to shine.
広い世界に存在を証明したくて
Wanting to prove my existence to this wide world.
出来ないことばかり数えても
Even if I only count what I cannot do,
胸が苦しくなるだけでしょう？
it will only make my chest ache, right?
私だって絶対 あの日の夢のようになれるはず
Even I should surely be able to reach that day's dream.
響く音色のなかほら
Look, within the echoing melody,
満ちてゆく景色
the scenery is filling up.
遠く感じてたのに 近づいていたんだ
Though it felt so far away, it was drawing closer.
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先
At the tip of this hand I softly reached out,
描いた理想像が想像を超える
the ideal image I drew surpasses my imagination.
やっと見つける私の色
Finally, I find my own color.
ずっと ずっと ずっと追いかけるの
I will chase it forever and ever.
鍵のかかった思い出たち
The memories that were locked away,
瞳に映るすべて
everything reflected in my eyes.
変わりゆく世界のリズム乗って
Riding the rhythm of a changing world,
モノクロ染めてゆく
I'll color the monochrome world.
不透明でもいいの
It's fine even if it's opaque,
不安感じても
even if I feel anxious.
私だけの色で描こう
Let's paint it with only my color.
きっと未来は色に溢れ
The future will surely overflow with color,
まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める
dyeing this yet-unseen world in color.
もっと自由に羽ばたくから
Because I will flap my wings even more freely...
ずっと あの日のままに
forever, just like that day.
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先
At the tip of this hand I softly reached out,
描いた理想像が想像を超える
the ideal image I drew surpasses my imagination.
やっと見つけた私の色
Finally, I found my own color.
ずっと ずっと ずっと描いてゆくの
I will keep on painting it forever and ever.
ありがとうー！
Thank you so much!
はい、というわけで
Alright, and with that...
まずは自己紹介からしたいと思うんですけど
First, I'd like to do our self-introductions,
あの...
um...
みんなも、わかってる人とわかってない人いるかもしれないから、一応説明するんですが
Some of you might know, and some might not, so let me explain just in case.
うちが「うち、うち、うちだよー！」って言ったら、みんな「大神ミオだよー！」って言ってもらったら、うちの自己紹介が完成するので
When I say "It's me, me, it's me!", if you all reply with "It's Ookami Mio!", my self-introduction will be complete!
言ってもらってもいいですか？
So, could you say that for me?
それじゃあ、行きますよー！
Alright then, here we go!
うち、うち、うちだよー！
It's me, me, it's me!
大神ミオだよー！
It's Ookami Mio!
わー！
Wow!
本日は、大神ミオのソロライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on holding Ookami Mio's solo live concert today!
あ、うちがおめでとうって言われる側だと思うんだけど、多分。
Ah, though I'm probably the one who should be congratulated, I think.
あははは。
Ahahaha.
すごい、みんな！
You guys are amazing!
え、ソロライブの衣装どうかな？
So, how do you like my solo live outfit?
可愛い？嬉しい！
Cute? I'm so glad!
なんと、なんと、今回、あの６年と、まあ、もうちょっとで７年活動してきて
And guess what? This time, after about 6 years—well, almost 7 years of activities—
尻尾が解放されてるんです！
my tails have been unleashed!
見て、見て！
Look, look!
今までずーっと、あ、あの...
Until now, they were always, um...
ここ、足にね、あの、巻き付いていたしっぽが...
Here, my tail that was wrapped around my leg...
見えちゃった感じなんですけれど。
...is now showing like this.
嬉しいな、なんか。
I'm so happy, somehow.
まぁこれはうちの自信の現れと言いますか。
Well, you could say this is a sign of my confidence.
自信がついたからこうやって、しっぽが解放できたということで。
Since I've gained confidence, I was able to free my tail like this.
はぁ...この舞台にうちを上げてくれたみんな、ありがとう！
Haa... Thank you to everyone who brought me to this stage!
はぁ...ちょっと汗かいてきちゃったかも。
Haa... I might have started sweating a little.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
いやぁ、ちょっとね、最初だし、
Wow, since it's the start,
コール＆レスポンスとかしてみたいけど、
I'd like to try doing a call and response,
どうかな？
what do you think?
じゃあやってみちゃおうかな。
Then, let's try it!
さっきね、あの、大神ミオにはなってもらったから、
Earlier, you guys chanted "Ookami Mio,"
おお、どうしようかな。
so, let's see, what should we do next?
じゃあ、えっと、「大神ミオ ソロライブ」って言ったら、みんな「アワースパークル！」って大きい声で言ってもらってもいいですか？
Well then, if I say "Ookami Mio Solo Live," could everyone say "Our Sparkle!" in a loud voice?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあ、いきますよ。
Alright, here we go!
大神ミオ ソロライブ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live!
アワースパークル！
Our Sparkle!
ありがとう！すっごいよく聞こえる！
Thank you! I heard you so clearly!
はぁ、ちょっとね。配信で見ている、
Haa... And also, to those watching the livestream,
そこの君も！つり席のみんなもよく見えてるよ、コメント！ありがとうね！
you over there! And everyone in the balcony seats, I can see your comments! Thank you!
いっぱいうちの可愛い姿をスクショしてもらえたら嬉しいなって思います。
I'd be happy if you took lots of screenshots of my cute self.
現地のみんなは一旦、記憶にキャプチャーしてね。
For those here at the venue, please capture it in your memory first!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、そして、ハッシュタグ「ミオスパークル」で、スクショや感想のポストもよろしくお願いします！
Also, please post your screenshots and thoughts with the hashtag #MioSparkle!
いやさ、もう、大神ミオソロライブ、始まっちゃったらもうあっという間に終わっちゃうのかと思うともうMCもまだまだ終わりたくないんだけど、
I mean, since Ookami Mio's Solo Live has started, I feel like it'll be over in the blink of an eye. I don't want this MC segment to end yet...
もう始まった瞬間から終わる心配してるんだけど。
...though I've been worrying about it ending since the very moment it started!
はい、今日はね、たくさん最高にキラキラな思い出作っていこうね！
Yes, let's make lots of the most sparkling memories today!
すごい！
Amazing!
はい、そして、チラ見せ枠のみなさんには、残念なお知らせなんですけれど、
Yes, and I have some sad news for those watching the sneak peek portion...
まぁあの、現地のみなさんは最後まで見れるのは確定なんですが、
Well, those at the venue are guaranteed to see it until the end, but...
無料配信はここで、お別れとなります。
...the free stream ends here.
はい、というわけでね、あの、配信のチケットを買っていただければ続きが見れますので、ぜひぜひ買っていただければなと、ミオファのみんなも思ってるよね？
Yes, so if you purchase a livestream ticket, you can watch the rest. I'm sure all of the Miofa think so too, right?
思ってます！買って！よろしくお願いします！
We do! Buy it! Please!
買う！買う！見たい！見たい！
We'll buy it! We want to watch!
見てほしいな！見逃すなよ！そうだそうだ！
We want you to watch! Don't miss it! Yeah, yeah!
ふふ、なんか、イマジナリーミオファの声が聞こえてくるような...
Haha, I feel like I can hear the voices of imaginary Miofa...
騒がしいミオファの声ですね。はい。
They are quite noisy Miofa indeed. Yes.
というわけで、そろそろ次の曲行きますか！
With that said, shall we move on to the next song?
大神ミオソロライブ、盛り上がっていくぞ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live, let's pump it up!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[On-Screen] The free preview has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.